Guide to the UE National Office Records Relating to District 4 and District 4 Locals, 1935-1991 UE.4.1.4
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- District 4 Locals, 2.
  - Local 408
    - Local 408 Outgoing Correspondence, April 28, 1936-November 20, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 63)
      - Arvidson to James Carey Regarding NLRB and Hatfield Wire and Cable Compnay, November 29, 1938; 9.
      - Arvidson to Emspak Regarding Hatfield Wire and Cable, December 19, 1938; 10.
      - Arvidson to William Mitchell Regarding Local 403 Hatfield Wire and Cable Negotiations, December 19, 1938; 11.
      - Arvidson to Emspak Regarding Local 403 Finances, January 24, 1939; 12.
      - Arvidson to James Matles Regarding Star Electric Company 1938 Wage Rates, April 11, 1939; 13.
      - Arvidson to J.B. Steckley Regarding Star Electric Company Wage Rates, April 13, 1939; 14.
      - Arvidson to Emspak Regarding Local 408 Star Electric Pending Disagreement, May 5, 1939; 15.
      - Arvidson to Matles Regarding Local 408 Star Electric Negotiations, May 19, 1939; 16.
      - Arvidson to Matles Regarding Columbia Cable and Electric Company International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Inter-union Rivalry, June 20, 1939; 17.
      - Arvidson to Emspak Regarding UE Locals and Electric Motors, Wire and Cable, August 16, 1939; 18.
      - Arvidson to Matles Regarding Local 408 Star Electric Contract, August 31, 1939; 19.
      - Arvidson to UE Regarding Local 408 Officers, October 12, 1939; 20.
      - Arvidson to Emspak Regarding Local 408 Star Electric Contract, October 25, 1939; 21.
      - Arvidson to Emspak, November 20, 1939; 22.
    - Local 408 Outgoing Correspondence, August 31, 1936-November 26, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 64)
      - Arvid Borg to Julius Emspak Regarding Local 408 Elections and Expulsion with 1937 Local 408 Ballot, July 1, 1937; 1.
      - Borg to UE, August 18-21, 1937; 2-3.
      - R.W. Berggrin to Emspak Regarding Local 408 Constitution and By-laws, January 12, 1941; 4.
      - William Hamilton Jr. to Emspak Regarding Local 408 Star Electric Negotiations, February 16-September 14, 1940; 5-6.
      - Hamilton to Emspak Regarding Local 408 Audit, September 17, 1945; 7.
      - Mildred Herman to Emspak Regarding Officers, April 4, 1944; 8.
      - Alfred Jensen to Emspak Regarding Stamps, January 16, 1945; 9.
      - Jensen to Emspak Regarding Veterans Dues and Finances, November 17, 1944; 10.
      - Jensen to Emspak Regarding Audit, December 12, 1944; 11.
      - Jensen to UE Regarding Supplies, May 29, 1945; 12.
      - William Machual to Emspak Regarding Officers, December 8, 1936; 13.
      - Joseph McGovern to Emspak Regarding UE Fort Wayne Convention, August 31, 1936; 14.
      - Carl Nilson to Emspak Regarding Withdrawal Card, November 8, 1937; 15.
      - Nilson to Emspak Regarding Philco Strike, July 22, 1938; 16.
      - Nilson to Emspak Regarding Stamps and Finances, December 19, 1938; 17.
      - Nilson to UE Regarding UE Strike Fund, May 9, 1939; 18.
      - Harry Palm to Emspak Regarding Local 408 Members, August 6-12, 1941; 19-20.
      - Palm to Emspak Regarding Mailing List, September 27, 1940; 21.
      - Palm to UE Regarding Local 408 Members, November 6, 1941-January 5, 1942; 22-24.
      - Palm to Emspak Regarding Per Capita, November 26, 1946; 25.
    - Local 408 Outgoing Correspondence, April 16, 1936-October 16, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 65)
      - Adrian Person to UE Regarding William Wellman Execution with Telegram to North Carolina Governor J.M. Broughton, December 15, 1942; 1.
      - Person to Julius Emspak Regarding Withdrawal Card, August 31, 1936; 2.
      - Person to Emspak Regarding Local 408 Officers, November 23, 1943; 3.
      - Guy Renga to UE Regarding UE Constitution and Amendments, November 4, 1946; 4.
      - Karl Rezac to Emspak Regarding Hatfield Wire and Cable Case Expenses, July 7, 1938; 5.
      - Charles Schirm, Jr. to James Carey Regarding Local 408 Buffalo Convention Delegates and UE Jurisdiction, April 16, 1936; 6.
      - Daniel Stenenson to UE News Editor Regarding Factional Struggle, July 14, 1941; 7.
      - George Tatoris to Political Action Committee, October 6, 1947; 8.
      - Joseph Voytac to James Matles Regarding Wage Rates, February 17-24, 1939; 9-10.
      - Albert Wills to UE Regarding UE Buffalo Convention Delegates, April 28, 1936; 11.
      - Wills to Emspak Regarding Per Capita and Supplies, May 5, 1936; 12.
    - Local 408 Salary and Expense Letters and Bonding Form, June 9, 1938-January 9, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 66)
      - Harry Palm, February 25, 1941-January 9, 1942; 1-6.
      - Bonding Form with Copy, June 9, 1938; 7.
    - Local 408 Correspondence, October 10, 1939-April 11, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 67)
      - Neil Brant to James Matles Regarding Hatfield Wire and Cable International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Inter-union Rivalry, October 10, 1939; 1.
      - "Star Electric Motor Company, Explanation of Bonus Plan" Memo, September 3, 1940; 2.
      - Memo Regarding Local 403 and Star Electric, April 11, 1945; 3.
  - Local 409
    - Local 409 Officers Lists, February 13, 1939-February 15, 1955 (Box 5, Folder 68)
    - Local 409 Incoming Correspondence, June 23, 1937-July 5, 1955 (Box 5, Folder 69)
      - William Cahn to Anthony Lizzano, August 20, 1947; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to Steven Bilecki Regarding Supplies and Transfers, June 23, 1937; 2.
      - Emspak to J.R. Matlack, July 8, 1938; 3.
      - Emspak to Matlack Regarding Member Transfers from Locals 411 and 415 to Local 409, July 20, 1938; 4.
      - Emspak to Matlack Regarding Busch Manufacturing, July 10, 1939; 5.
      - Emspak to Matlack Regarding Expenses, May 27, 1940; 6.
      - Emspak to Frank Giorgianni Regarding Overtime, October 5, 1942; 7.
      - Emspak to Matlack Regarding Mailing List, October 31-November 18, 1940; 8-9.
      - Emspak to D. DiPietro Regarding Local 409 Debt, February 17-March 15, 1941; 10-11.
      - Emspak to John Scarantino Regarding Mailing List, November 7, 1941; 12.
      - Emspak to Anna Mirabelli Regarding Contract, May 11, 1944; 13.
      - Emspak to Elizabeth Nussbaum Regarding Veterans Initiation Fees, August 9, 1945; 14.
      - Emspak to John Dobyns Regarding Per Capita, January 23, 1947; 15.
      - Emspak to Lizzano, December 4, 1947; 16.
      - Emspak to Dobyns Regarding Supplies, December 4, 1947; 17.
      - Emspak to Local 409 Regarding Supplies, February 5, 1951; 18.
      - Emspak to Blacey Immordino Regarding National Strike Fund, November 19, 1952; 19.
      - Emspak to Local 409 Regarding National Strike Fund, January 6, 1953; 20.
      - Emspak to Immordino Regarding National Strike Fund, February 16, 1953; 21.
      - Emspak to Lizzano, August 6, 1953; 22.
      - Emspak to Lizzano Regarding Local 409 Cramer-Trenton Strike, June 17, 1955; 23.
      - Emspak to Stanley Krzywonos Regarding Supplies, June 23, 1955; 24.
      - Emspak to Lizzano Regarding Local 409 Cramer-Trenton Strike with Memo Regarding Strike Contributions, June 29, 1955; 25.
      - Emspak to Lizzano Regarding Local 409 Cramer-Trenton Strike, July 5, 1955; 26.
    - Local 409 Incoming Correspondence, December 30, 1940-May 2, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 70)
      - Albert Fitzgerald to Local 409, August 27, 1942; 1.
      - Fitzgerald to Anthony Lizzano, August 21, 1947; 2.
      - Fitzgerald to Peter Besch Regarding Transfer, November 24, 1947; 3.
      - Fitzgerald to Mary Welsh Regarding Transfer, November 24, 1947; 4.
      - Fitzgerald to Lizzano, August 6, 1953, August 10, 1954; 5-6.
      - Nathan Geller to John Scarantino Regarding Supplies, May 14, 1941; 7.
      - James Matles to J.R. Matlack Regarding Trenton Organization, December 30, 1940-February 11, 1941; 8-9.
      - Matles to Scarantino Regarding Forms, April 30, 1941; 10.
      - Matles to Lizzano, August 20, 1947; 11.
      - Matles to Lizzano Regarding Local 120 Baltimore Locke Insulator Company, January 19, 1951; 12.
      - Matles to William Love Regarding Locals 409 and 109 and International Representatives' Finances, December 31, 1952; 13.
      - Matles to Lizzano Regarding Local 409 Annual Picnic, August 6, 1953, August 24, 1954; 14-15.
      - Matles to Lizzano Regarding Local 107 Westinghouse Strike, May 2, 1956; 16.
    - Local 409 Incoming Correspondence, April 13, 1937-April 13, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 71)
      - William Mitchell to Alfred Wishart Regarding Trenton Organization, April 13, 1937; 1.
      - Mitchell to Robert Immordino Regarding Unemployment, November 16, 1937; 2.
      - Mitchell to Immordino Regarding Trenton Auto Radiator, April 13, 1938; 3.
      - Mitchell to Immordino Regarding Auto Radiator Organization, April 13, 1937; 4.
      - Executive Secretary to Immordino Regarding Auto Radiator Organization, April 19, 1937; 5.
    - Local 409 Outgoing Correspondence, June 20, 1937-June 21, 1955 (Box 5, Folder 72)
      - Steven Belecki to UE Regarding Transfers and Bookkeeping, June 20, 1937; 1.
      - Daneil Cohen to James Carey, September 14, 1938; 2.
      - Ezra Counts to Harold Kraemer Regarding Grievance, October 5, 1950; 3.
      - Frank Giorgianni to James Matles Regarding Contract and Negotiations, March 24, 1942; 4.
      - Giorgianni to Matles Regarding Shell Casing Price List, April 2, 1942; 5.
      - Giorgianni to Julius Emspak, September 30, 1942; 6.
      - Mark Hawley to Emspak, November 16, 1943; 7.
      - Robert Immordino to Bill Mitchell Regarding Loan, November 15, 1937; 8.
      - R. Immordino to Matles, November 15, 1937; 9.
      - R. Immordino to Emspak Regarding Supplies, December 15, 1937; 10.
      - R. Immordino to Mitchell Regarding Local 409 Kramer's Coils and Trenton Auto Radiator Contract Negotiations, April 5, 1938; 11.
      - Blacey Immordino to General Cable Workers Regarding Strike, October 28, 1952; 12.
      - Stanley Krzywonos to Matles Regarding Officers, March 19, 1941; 13.
      - Krzywonos to Mr. Wright Regarding C.V. Hill Company Organization, March 18, 1943; 14.
      - Krzywonos to Emspak Regarding Supplies, June 21, 1955; 15.
      - Anthony Lizzano to Emspak Regarding Annual Outing, August 7, 1947; 16.
      - Lizzano to Matles Regarding Annual Outing, August 7, 1947; 17.
      - Lizzano to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Annual Outing, August 7, 1947; 18.
      - Lizzano to UE Regarding Supplies, August 18, 1947; 19.
      - Lizzano to Matles and Emspak Regarding Support for Officers at the Unamerican Committee, September 14, 1951; 20.
    - Local 409 Outgoing Correspondence, February 19, 1939-July 13, 1955 (Box 5, Folder 73)
      - Anthony Lizzano to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Annual Outing with August 6, 1953, Union News, August 5, 1953; 1.
      - Lizzano to Julius Emspak Regarding Annual Outing, August 5, 1953; 2.
      - Lizzano to James Matles Regarding Annual Outing, August 5, 1953, August 14, 1954; 3-4.
      - Lizzano to Emspak Regarding Annual Outing, August 14, 1945; 5.
      - Lizzano to Fitzgerald Regarding Annual Outing, August 14, 1954; 6.
      - Lizzano to Emspak Regarding Local 409 Kramer-Trenton Strike, July 13, 1955; 7.
      - William Love et al to James Matles Regarding Peter Besch Lay-off, December 5, 1952; 8.
      - J.R. Matlack to Matles Regarding People's Press, February 19, 1939; 9.
      - Matlack to Matles Regarding Wage Rates, March 4, 1939; 10.
      - Matlack to Emspak Regarding Busch Manufacturing Company, July 6, 1939; 11.
      - Matlack to Matles Regarding Local 409 Membership, October 9, 1939; 12.
      - Matlack to Matles Regarding Trenton Organization, December 29, 1940; 13.
      - Matlack to Ray Klausner Regarding Trenton Organization, February 4, 1941; 14.
      - Anna Mirabelli to Emspak Regarding Officers, March 24, 1944; 15.
      - Mirabelli to UE Regarding Contract Negotiations, May 9, 1944; 16.
      - Elizabeth Nussbaum to UE Regarding Veterans Initiation Stamps, August 8, 1945; 17.
      - John J. Scarantino to James Carey Regarding Strike and Contract, April 23, 1941; 18.
      - Vincent Trapani to UE Regarding Strike, June 20, 1955; 19.
      - John Worth to Emspak Regarding Strike, June 20-July 1, 1955; 20-21.
      - Outing Committee Chairman to UE Regarding Annual Outing, August 27, 1942; 22.
    - Local 409 Bonding Forms, June 21-28, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 74)
    - Local 409 Treasury Shortage, February 1942 (Box 5, Folder 75)
      - John McDonough to Julius Emspak, February 1942; 1.
      - Emspak to McDonough, February 14, 1942; 2.
      - McDonough to Emspak, February 22, 1942; 3.
    - Local 409 American Federation of Labor Inter-union Rivalry, September 1942 (Box 5, Folder 76)
      - Frank Giorgianni to Julius Emspak, September 1942; 1.
      - James Matles to John McDonough, September 28, 1942; 2.
    - Local 409 New Jersey Porcelain, January 7-16, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 77)
      - Walter Barry to James Matles with Stanley Krzyonos Letter, January 7, 1947; 1.
      - David Ratner to Barry, January 16, 1947; 2.
    - Local 409 Correspondence, March 18, 1941, February 26, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 78)
      - Officers, March 18, 1941; 1.
      - Peter Besch to James Matles Regarding Local 409 Kramer-Trenton Strike, February 26, 1952; 2.
    - Local 409 Publications, February 22, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 79)
      - "UE Local 409 Bulletin", 1.
      - Press Release, Febrauary 22, 1952; 2.
    - Local 409 Newspaper Clippings, February 23-26, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 80)
      - "Work Stoppage Hits 300 at Local Plant," Trentonian, February 23, 1952; 1.
      - "Employees Out, Kramer Plant Closed Down," Trenton Times, February 24, 1952; 2.
      - "Labor Dispute at Kramer Company Still Unsettled," Trentonian, February 26, 1952; 3.
  - Local 410
    - Local 410 Constitution and By-laws, November 1, 1939-September 27, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 81)
      - Constitution and By-laws of UE, November 1, 1939; 1.
      - Constitution and By-laws of Local 410, September 27, 1946; 2.
    - Local 410 Officers Lists, 1941-1949 (Box 5, Folder 82)
      - Officers Lists, 1941-1949; 1-7.
      - Officers List with September 22, 1949, Pauline Royce Letter to Julius Emspak, September 1949; 8.
    - Local 410 Incoming Correspondence, January 9, 1939-March 11, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 83)
      - Neil Brant to Stanley Newton Regarding Local 410 Westinghouse Collective Bargaining, April 22, 1940; 1.
      - William Cahn to Richard Lynch Regarding Radio Broadcasts, March 11, 1948; 2.
      - James Carey to Mildred Donaldson Regarding Local 410 Officers, January 9, 1939; 3.
      - Carey to Lynch, January 19, 1939; 4.
      - Carey to Lynch Regarding Employees Independent Union, March 31, 1939; 5.
      - Carey to Lynch Regarding Membership Meeting, January 9, 1940; 6.
      - Carey to Donaldson Regarding Membership Meeting, February 15, 1940; 7.
      - Carey to Donaldson Regarding Women and Dues, January 30, 1941; 8.
      - Joseph Dermody to Lynch Regarding St. Louis General Electric Women and Wages with December 13, 1946, Wages, December 23, 1946; 9.
    - Local 410 Incoming Correspondence, June 8, 1937-December 10, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 84)
      - Julius Emspak to Stanley Newton Regarding Supplies, June 8, 1937; 1.
      - Emspak to Mildred Donaldson Regarding Mailing List, August 12, 1937; 2.
      - Emspak to K.A. Tyrrell Regarding Dues and Supplies, March 26, 1938; 3.
      - Emspak to Newton Regarding Women and Dues, February 6, 1939; 4.
      - Emspak to Donaldson Regarding Westinghouse Locals with Westinghouse Locals Address List, July 6, 1939; 5.
      - Emspak to Newton Regarding Lamp Industry Organization, Wages, Women and General Electric, September 22, 1939; 6.
      - Emspak to Newton Regarding Bloomfield Westinghouse Organization, December 12, 1939; 7.
      - Emspak to Donaldson Regarding Bloomfield Westinghouse Organization, February 20, 1940; 8.
      - Emspak to Newton Regarding Mailing List, September 13-November 8, 1940; 9-11.
      - Emspak to William Twist Regarding Mailing List, May 14, 1941; 12.
      - Emspak to William Campbell Regarding Publication, July 30, 1941; 13.
      - Emspak to Campbell, October 27, 1941; 14.
      - Emspak to Ray Jenkins Regarding Belleville, September 24, 1942; 15.
      - Emspak to Jenkins Regarding Providence Base Works, April 23, 1943; 16.
      - Emspak to Richard Lynch Regarding Workmen's Compensation, November 24, 1943; 17.
      - Emspak to James Fitzpatrick Regarding Political Action Committee, November 10, 1944; 18.
      - Emspak to Lynch Regarding Wages, December 13, 1944; 19.
      - Emspak to Twist Regarding Westinghouse Strikes, April 30, 1946; 20.
      - Emspak to Twist Regarding Finances, December 10, 1946; 21.
    - Local 410 Incoming Correspondence, March 22, 1944-March 23, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 85)
      - Julius Emspak to William Twist Regarding Finances, January 17, 1947; 1.
      - Emspak to Richard Lynch Regarding Political Action, January 27, 1947; 2.
      - Emspak to Lynch Regarding Local 410 Officers, June 4, 1947; 3.
      - Emspak to Arthur McBride Regarding Per Capita, July 7-17, 1947; 4-5.
      - Emspak to Walter Graczyk Regarding Grievances, April 19, 1948; 6.
      - Emspak to Lynch Regarding Finances, October 25, 1948; 7.
      - Albert Fitzgerald to Lynch Regaridng Local 410 Officers, March 22, 1944; 8.
      - Fitzgerald to Walter Zack Regarding War Labor Board, August 7, 1944; 9.
      - Fitzgerald to Lynch Regarding Finances, August 7, 1944; 10.
      - Fitzgerald to E. Del Guidice Regarding WLB, August 7, 1944; 11.
      - Fitzgerald to John Gorman Regarding WLB, August 7, 1944; 12.
      - Fitzgerald to Ellen Suggs Regarding Local 410 Officers and UE Constitution, June 12, 1947; 13.
      - Fitzgerald to Graczyk Regarding Factionalism, February 17, 1948; 14.
      - Fitzgerald to Lynch Regarding Graczyk Case and Factionalism, February 24, 1948; 15.
      - Fitzgerald to Graczyk Regarding Factionalism, February 25, 1948; 16.
      - Fitzgerald to Lynch Regarding Membership Meeting, March 23, 1949; 17.
      - Ray Klausner to Lynch Regarding Bloomfield Congress of Industrial Organizations Rally, August 22, 1945; 18.
    - Local 410 Incoming Correspondence, November 29, 1938-July 19, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 86)
      - James Matles to Mildred Donaldson Regarding Westinghouse Organization, November 29, 1938; 1.
      - Matles to Richard Lynch Regarding Membership Meeting, April 14, 1939; 2.
      - Matles to Lynch Regarding Local 107 Political Action, June 13, 1939; 3.
      - Matles to Lynch Regarding Membership Meeting, June 21, 1939; 4.
      - Matles Telegram to Stanley Newton Regarding Lima Westinghouse Organization, August 18, 1939; 5.
      - Matles to Newton Regarding Westinghouse Conference, October 3, 1939; 6.
      - Matles to Newton Regarding National Labor Relations Board and Westinghouse with October 17, 1939, H.D. Madden Letter to Matles, October 18, 1939; 7.
      - Matles to Newton Regarding Derry Westinghouse Organization, December 22, 1939; 8.
      - Matles to Lynch Regarding Membership Meeting, January 18, 1940; 9.
      - Matles to Newton Regarding Lamp Industry Organization, January 24, 1940; 10.
      - Matles to Lynch Regarding Cleveland General Electric and NLRB, February 14, 1940; 11.
      - Matles to Robert Humphry Regarding Wages, April 15-June 3, 1940; 12-13.
      - Matles to Newton Regarding Westinghouse Organizaiton and General Electric Collective Bargaining, June 12, 1940; 14.
      - Matles to Newton Regarding Local 410 Westinghouse Collective Bargaining, December 3, 1940; 15.
      - Matles to Newton Regarding Wages, December 9, 1940; 16.
      - Matles to Newton Regarding Grievances, January 7, 1941; 17.
      - Matles to William Campbell Regarding Local 410 Westinghouse Contract, April 29, 1941; 18.
      - Matles to Donaldson Regarding Fairmont Westinghouse Organization, July 18, 1941; 19.
      - Matles Telegram to Newton Regarding Westinghouse Collective Bargaining, May 2, 1942; 20.
      - Matles to Lynch Regarding Foreman, January 25, 1943; 21.
      - Matles to Arthur Weidlich Regarding War Manpower Commission, February 11, 1943; 22.
      - Matles to Lynch Regarding Owensboro General Electric and United Auto Workers, July 19, 1946; 23.
    - Local 410 Incoming Correspondence, May 15, 1944-April 20, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 87)
      - James Matles to Richard Lynch Regarding Corning Glass Wages, January 24, 1947; 1.
      - Matles to Lynch Regarding Kentucky Westinghouse Organization, April 9, 1947; 2.
      - Matles to Lynch Regarding Publicity, May 14, 1947; 3.
      - Matles to Lynch Regarding Swanson Tool, Wages and United Auto Workers with March 11, 1948, Fred Gardner Letter to Matles, March 20, 1948; 4.
      - Matles to Lynch Regarding Richmond and Little Rock Westinghouse Organization and Wages, March 29, 1948; 5.
      - Matles to Lynch Regarding Richmond Westinghouse Organization and Staff Members, July 6, 1948; 6.
      - Matles to Lynch Regarding Richmond Westinghouse Organization, July 16, 1948; 7.
      - Matles to Lynch Regarding Membership Drive, April 20, 1949; 8.
      - David Ratner to Lynch Regarding Staff Members, November 21, 1945; 9.
      - William Sentner to Lynch Regarding Little Rock Westinghouse and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Inter-union Rivalry, August 23, 1948; 10.
      - Nat Spero to Lynch Regarding Inflation, May 31, 1944; 11.
      - A.N. Towsen to Lynch Regarding Buffalo Organization and Wages, May 15, 1944; 12.
      - Townsen to H.W. Conklin Regarding Falk Publishing, March 13, 1944; 13.
    - Local 410 Outgoing Correspondence, November 1937-Februray 1948 (Box 5, Folder 88)
      - William Campbell Telegram to James Matles Regarding Local 410 Westinghouse Contract, April 26, 1941; 1.
      - Campbell to Matles Regarding Women and Wages, September 22, 1941; 2.
      - Mildred Donaldson to UE Regarding Membership, November 1937; 3.
      - Donaldson to Matles Regarding Bloomfield Westinghouse Organization, November 28, 1938; 4.
      - Donaldson to James Carey Regarding Local 410 Officers, December 26, 1938; 5.
      - Donaldson to Julius Emspak Regarding Union Label, January 22, 1939; 6.
      - Donaldson to Emspak Regarding Belleville Westinghouse Organization, February 13, 1939; 7.
      - Donaldson to Carey Regarding Membership Meeting, October 28, 1939; 8.
      - Donaldson to Emspak Regarding Supplies, February 1, 1940; 9.
      - Donaldson to Carey Regarding Local 410 Officers, February 1, 1940; 10.
      - Donaldson to Carey Regarding Membership Meeting, February 4-13, 1940; 11-12.
      - Donaldson to Carey Regarding Congress of Industrial Organizations Political Action, November 7, 1940; 13.
      - Donaldson to Emspak Regarding Wages, December 7, 1940; 14.
      - Donaldson to Carey Regarding Dues and Women, February 7, 1941; 15.
      - James Fitzpatrick to Emspak Regarding Finances, November 14, 1944; 16.
      - Verna Fix to Emspak Regarding Westinghouse Conference, February 7, 1942; 17.
      - Fix to Matles Regarding War Manpower Commission, January 26, 1943; 18.
      - Walter Graczyk to UE Regarding Seniority and Factionalism, July 9, 1947; 19.
      - Graczyk to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Seniority and Factionalism, February 1948; 20-21.
    - Local 410 Outgoing Correspondence, January 15, 1938-July 30, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 89)
      - Robert Humphry to James Matles Regarding Wages, April 8, 1940; 1.
      - Humphry to Matles Regarding Wages and Women, May 28, 1940; 2.
      - Ray Jenkins to Julius Emspak Regarding Supplies, August 1940; 3.
      - Jenkins to Matles Regarding Local 410 Westinghouse Contract, February 7, 1942; 4.
      - Jenkins Telegram to Matles Regarding Local 410 Westinghouse Contract, July 30, 1942; 5.
      - Richard Lynch to James Carey Regarding Bloomfield Westinghouse and Catholic Church, January 15, 1938; 6.
      - Lynch to Emspak Regarding Publicity, Catholic Church and Bloomfield Westinghouse, March 22, 1939; 7.